Kheel Center Current Documents Correspondence /4212
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Westinghouse, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  May 7 1962
- William-Frederick Press (Box 3, Folder 74)
- Wilson Company, H.W., 1962-1964 (Box 3, Folder 75)
- Wisconsin. Employment Relations Commission, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 76)
- State Historical Society of Wisconsin, 1953-1969 (Box 3, Folder 77)
- University of Wisconsin, 1961-1977 (Box 3, Folder 78)
- Alan Wood Steel Company, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  June 28 1965
- World Federation of Trade Unions, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  April, May and October 1964
- Worthington Corporation (Box 3, Folder 81)
  Paper slip
- Xerox Corporation, 1966-1968 (Box 3, Folder 82)
- Yagoda, Louis, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  January 1967
- Yale University, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  January 14 1975
- Youngstown Sheet and Tube Company, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 85)
- Zenith Radio Company, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  November 12 1953
- AFL-CIO, 1956-1977 (Box 3, Folder 87)
- AFL-CIO Agricultural Workers Organizing Committee, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  January and February 1965
- AFL-CIO Auxiliaries, 1964-1967 (Box 3, Folder 89)
- AFL-CIO Building and Construction Trades Department, 1952-1976 (Box 3, Folder 90)
- AFL-CIO Committee on Political Education, 1957-1972 (Box 3, Folder 91)
- AFL-CIO Community Service Activities, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 92)
- AFL-CIO Council for AFL-CIO Unions for Professional Employees, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  February 1976
- AFL-CIO Education Department, 1957-1968 (Box 3, Folder 94)
- AFL-CIO. Food and Beverage Trades Department, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  November 14 1977
- AFL-CIO Human Resources Development Institute, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  October 1969
- AFL-CIO Industrial Union Department, 1957-1977 (Box 3, Folder 97)
- AFL-CIO Library, 1965-1969 (Box 3, Folder 98)
- AFL-CIO Maritime Trades Department, 1961-1977 (Box 3, Folder 99)
- AFL-CIO Metal Trades Department, 1958-1963 (Box 3, Folder 100)
- AFL-CIO Organization Department, 1965-1968 (Box 3, Folder 101)
- AFL-CIO Publication Department, 1959-1967 (Box 3, Folder 102)
- AFL-CIO Railway Employees' Department, 1960-1964 (Box 3, Folder 103)
- AFL-CIO Union Label and Service Trades Department, 1958-1969 (Box 3, Folder 104)
- Actors' Equity Association, 1972-1977 (Box 3, Folder 105)
- Actors and Artists. Musical Artists, 1955-1977 (Box 3, Folder 106)
- Actors and Artists. Television and Radio Artists, 1955-1972 (Box 3, Folder 107)
- Actors and Artists. Screen Actors Guild, 1959-1972 (Box 3, Folder 108)
- Actors and Artists. Variety Artists, 1956-1970 (Box 3, Folder 109)
- African-American Labor Center, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 110)
  September, October and November 1967
- Airline Dispatchers Association, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 111)
  November 1964
- Airline Employees Association International, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  November 15 1967
- Airline Pilots Association, 1969-1974 (Box 3, Folder 113)
- Air Traffic Controllers Organization. Professional, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  April 16 1971
- Alberta Federation of Labor, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 115)
  June 21 1962
- Alliance of Independent Telephone Unions, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  December 15 1975
- Alliance for Labor Action (Box 3, Folder 117)
- Allied Pilots Association, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 118)
  January, July and August 1975
- Aluminum Workers International Union, 1961-1978 (Box 3, Folder 119)
- Amalgamated Bank of New York, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 120)
  November 1 1966
- American Institute for Free Labor, 1962-1969 (Box 3, Folder 121)
- American Nurses Association, 1965-1968 (Box 3, Folder 122)
- Arizona State AFL-CIO, 1962-1969 (Box 3, Folder 123)
- Arkansas State AFL-CIO, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 124)
  August 10 1967
- Asian Labor Education Center (Philippines), 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 125)
- Associated Actors and Artists of America, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 126)
  July 1 1975
- Australian Workers Union, 1966-1975 (Box 3, Folder 127)
- Automobile Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of American International Union, 1953-1973 (Box 3, Folder 128)
- Bakery and Confectionary Workers' International Union of America, 1949-1977 (Box 3, Folder 129)
- International Association of Barbers, Beauticians and Allied Industries, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 130)
  February 24 1978
- Baseball Players Association. Major League, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 131)
  February 25 1969
- National Basketball Players Association, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 132)
- Boilermakers. Iron Ship Makers. International Union., 1965-1972 (Box 3, Folder 133)
  December 14 1965 - January 7 1972
- International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers of America (AFL-CIO), 1962-1972 (Box 3, Folder 134)
  March 7 1962 - January 6 1972
- United Brick and Clay Workers of America, 1967-1976 (Box 3, Folder 135)
  November 13 1967 - October 8 1976
- Bricklayers Union, 1966-1972 (Box 3, Folder 136)
  September 12 1966 - January 4 1972
- British Guiana Mineworker's Union, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 137)
  February and April 1962
- National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians, 1968-1971 (Box 3, Folder 138)
  June 4 1968 - December 23 1971
- Building Service Employees' International Union, 1962-1968 (Box 3, Folder 139)
  April 18 1962 - September 23 1968
- California Labor Federation, 1963-1968 (Box 3, Folder 140)
  November 1 1963 - September 12 1968
- California State Employees' Association, 1962-1964 (Box 3, Folder 141)
  May 21 1962 - January 6 1964
- Canada. Economic Security Employees' National Association, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 142)
  December 19 1967
- Canada. Fraternite Des Policiers de Montreal, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 143)
  French and English. November 24 1969 - February 4 1970
- Canada. Ontario Federation of Labour, 1967-1970 (Box 3, Folder 144)
- Canadian Brotherhood of Railway, Transport and General Workers (Box 3, Folder 145)
- Canadian Labour Congress. Congres Du Travail du Canada, 1964-1971 (Box 3, Folder 146)
  French and English
- Canadian Labour Congress. Quebec Federation of Labour, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 147)
- Canadian Union of Public Employees, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 148)
  September, October and November 1973
- United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1967-1972 (Box 3, Folder 149)
- Carpenters and Joiners of America Western Council. Lumber and Sawmill Workers, 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 150)
  November 16 1962 - November 20 1963
- Association of Catholic Trade Unionists, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 151)
  March 28 1968
- International Union of Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers, 1962-1971 (Box 3, Folder 152)
- Central Council of Hungarian Trade Unions, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 153)
  October 17 1977 - February 8 1978
- Central Council of Trade Unions, 1963-1968 (Box 3, Folder 154)
  March 26 1963 - April 10 1968
- International Chemical Workers Union, 1962-1973 (Box 3, Folder 155)
  October 4 1962 - June 21 1973
- Civil Service Employees Association, Inc., 1962-1977 (Box 3, Folder 156)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1952-1970 (Box 3, Folder 157)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 158)
  April 4 1978
- AFL-CIO Colorado Labor Council, 1963-1970 (Box 3, Folder 159)
  February 1 1963 - June 23 1970
- Committee of Interns and Residents, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 160)
  May 25 1978
- Communications Workers of America, 1962-1977 (Box 3, Folder 161)
- Confederated Independent Unions, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 162)
  September 26 1972
- Confederation of National Trade Unions, 1962-1977 (Box 3, Folder 163)
  July 25 1962 - September 29 1977
- Confederation of National Trade Unions. Canada, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 164)
  April 26 1967
- Conference of Transportation Trades, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 165)
  March, April and May 1970
- Congress of Railway Unions, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 166)
  January 19 1970
- Cornell University of Concerned Non-Academic Employees, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 167)
  June 1970
- Distillery, Rectifying, Wine and Allied Workers' International Union of America, 1965-1976 (Box 3, Folder 168)
  January 21 1965 - April 13 1976
- Distributive Workers of America, District 65, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 169)
  March 20 1978
- International Union of Dolls, Toys, Playthings, Novelties and Allied Products, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 170)
  October 7 1977
- Egyptian Federation of Labour, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 171)
  February 1 1978
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1966-1977 (Box 3, Folder 172)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 3, 1960-1977 (Box 3, Folder 173)
  October 3 1960 - October 7 1977
- United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America (IND), 1961-1971 (Box 3, Folder 174)
- International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers (AFL-CIO), 1962-1973 (Box 3, Folder 175)
- International Union of Elevator Constructors, 1971-1977 (Box 3, Folder 176)
  December 29 1971 - September 29 1977
- Amalgamated Union of Engineering Workers, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 177)
  February, April and September 1973
- Council of Engineers and Scientists, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 178)
  December 23 1968 - January 1969
- International Union of Operating Engineers, 1964-1972 (Box 3, Folder 179)
- American Federation of Technical Engineers, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 180)
  January 4 1972
- United Farm Workers of America, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 181)
  November 16 1977 - June 1 1978
- National Federation of Federal Employees, 1962-1968 (Box 3, Folder 182)
  November 1 1962 - June 13 1968
- Federatie Nederlandse Vakbeweging, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 183)
  Dutch and English. January 12 1978
- International Association of Firefighters, 1963-1972 (Box 3, Folder 184)
- International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 185)
  December 29 1971
- Flight Engineers' International Association, 1962-1964 (Box 3, Folder 186)
- Florida AFL-CIO, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 187)
- National Football League Players Association, 1972-1977 (Box 3, Folder 188)
  October 5 1972 - December 7 1977
- Fraternite des Policiers de La Communaute de Montreal Inc., 1977 (Box 3, Folder 189)
  French and English. June 15 1977
- Freier Deutscher Gewerkschaftsbund, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 190)
  German and English. February 10 1978
- United Furniture Workers of America, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 191)
  December 29 1971 - October 23 1972
- International Ladies Garment Workers, 1963-1978 (Box 3, Folder 192)
- United Garment Workers of America, 1963-1970 (Box 3, Folder 193)
  July 3 1963 - March 13 1970
- Granite Cutter's International Association of America, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 194)
- General Federation of Labor in Israel (American Representative), 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 195)
  English and Hebrew. July 18 1963 - December 23 1965
- Glass Bottle Blowers Association, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 196)
  July 22 1976
- United Glass and Ceramic Workers of North America, 1949-1976 (Box 3, Folder 197)
  December 12 1949 - October 8 1976
- Glass Workers' Union of North America. American Flint. AFL-CIO, 1962-1978 (Box 3, Folder 198)
  February 23 1962 - March 28 1978
- American Federation of Government Employees, 1962-1972 (Box 3, Folder 199)
- National Association of Government Employees, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 200)
  September 6 1972
- Government Employees' Council AFL-CIO, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 201)
  May 14 1963
- American Federation of Grain Millers, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 202)
  December 29 1971 - February 3 1972
- Granite Cutters International Association, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 203)
  October 8 1976 - October 3 1977
- Graphic Arts International Union, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 204)
  November 29 1972 - October 31 1973
- United Hatters, Cap and Millinery Workers International Union, 1965-1976 (Box 3, Folder 205)
- New York Hotel and Motel Trades Council, 1958-1966 (Box 3, Folder 206)
  November 7 1958 - September 16 1966
- Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1962-1972 (Box 3, Folder 207)
  December 10 1962 - January 5 1972
- Hotel Trades Council of N.Y.C., 1967 (Box 3, Folder 208)
  October 6 - 23 1967
- Human Resources Development Institute, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 209)
- Illinois State Federation of Labor, 1962-1964 (Box 3, Folder 210)
  November 28 1962 - May 6 1964
- National Federation of Independent Unions, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 211)
- International Union of Allied Industrial Workers of America, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 212)
  November 8 1971
- Industrial Workers of the World, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 213)
  September 17 1969 - May 25 1970
- Institute of International Labor Research Inc., 1965 (Box 3, Folder 214)
  December 29 1965
- International Union of Life Insurance Agents, 1965-1975 (Box 3, Folder 215)
  February 11 1965 - March 17 1975
- International Union of Insurance Workers, 1967-1971 (Box 3, Folder 216)
  October 10 1967 - December 29 1971
- ICFTU African Labour College (Box 3, Folder 217)
- ICFTU African Regional Organization, 1965-1968 (Box 3, Folder 218)
  August 20 1965 - February 28 1968
- ICFTU Asian Regional Organization, 1955-1964 (Box 3, Folder 219)
- ICFTU Asian Trade Union College, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 220)
  November 16 1965
- ICFTU European Regional Organization (Box 3, Folder 221)
- ICFTU Inter-American Regional Organization of Workers, 1960-1966 (Box 3, Folder 222)
- ICFU Trade Union Advisory Committee to OECD, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 223)
  January 16 1967
- ICFTU United Nations Office, 1957-1966 (Box 3, Folder 224)
  June 10 1957 - September 30 1966
- ICFTU Head Office (Brussels, Belgium), 1957-1967 (Box 3, Folder 225)
  June 18 1957 - February 2 1967
- National Association of Internal Revenue Employees, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 226)
  February 3 1972
- International Federation of Air Line Pilots Association, 1953-1962 (Box 3, Folder 227)
  August 4 1953 - December 5 1962
- T.S. International Federation of Building and Woodworkers, 1965-1967 (Box 3, Folder 228)
  November 30 1965 - November 14 1967
- T.S. International Federation of Chemical and General Workers Unions, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 229)
  June 1966 - October 31 1967
- T.S. International Federation of Commercial and Technical Employees, 1963-1972 (Box 3, Folder 230)
- T.S. International Federation of Free Teachers' Unions, 1963-1968 (Box 3, Folder 231)
  April 18 1963 - April 1 1968
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 232)
  August, November and December 1977
- T.S. International Federation of Petroleum and Chemical Workers, 1963-1967 (Box 3, Folder 233)
- T.S. International Federation of Plantation, Agricultural and Allied Workers, 1962-1967 (Box 3, Folder 234)
  January 11 1962 - February 2 1967
- International Federation of Workers' Educational Association, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 235)
- T.S. International Graphical Federation (Box 3, Folder 236)
- T.S. International Metalworkers Federation, 1969-1978 (Box 3, Folder 237)
  November 4 1969 - June 19 1978
- T.S. International Secretariat of Entertainment Trade Unions, 1965-1973 (Box 3, Folder 238)
  August 20 1965 - July 2 1973
- T.S. International Shoe and Leather Workers' Federation (Box 3, Folder 239)
- T.S. International Textile and Garment Workers' Federation, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 240)
  January 26 1967 - March 6 1967
- T.S. International Transport Workers' Federation, 1961-1971 (Box 3, Folder 241)
  March 4 1961 - February 18 1971
- T.S. International Union of Food and Allied Workers' Associations, 1963-1973 (Box 3, Folder 242)
  April 18 1963 - July 12 1973
- Iowa Federation of Labor, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 243)
- Ithaca Labor Committee, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 244)
  February 18 1970
- International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 245)
  March 28 1972
- International Jewelry Workers' Union, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  June 26 1967
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  July 14 1964 - April 1965
- John Herling's Labor Letter, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  January and November 1973
- Kansas State Federation of Labor, 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Kentucky State AFL-CIO, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  January 30 1967
- "Labor" Published by Unions Representing Railroad, Airline and Other Workers, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Labor Bureau of the Middle West, 1954-1965 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Labor Policy Association, Inc., 1965 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  December 2 1965
- Labor Research Association, 1962-1965 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Laborers' International Union, 1968-1972 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- International Ladies Garment Workers Union. Northeast Region, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  September 7 1978
- Landsorganisationen I Danmark, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  April 27 1978. English and Danish.
- Wood, Wire and Metal Lathers International Union, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  January 1968
- League for Industrial Democracy, 1962-1965 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- International Leather Goods, Plastics and Novelty Workers' Union, 1963-1977 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Leather Workers International Union, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  May 6 1976
- National Association of Letter Carriers, 1964-1972 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Amalgamated Lithographers of America, 1962-1965 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Lithographers and Photoengravers International Union, 1967-1971 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union International (IND) (Box 4, Folder 21)
- International Longshoremen's Association, 1965-1976 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Louisiana AFL-CIO, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  June 8 1967
- International Association of Machinists, 1962-1972 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- International Mailers Union, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  August 14 1963
- Maine State Federated Labor Council, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  March 31 1965
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1964-1973 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Association of Maintenance of Way and Miscellaneous Foreman on the Santa Fe, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  October and November 1966
- International Association of Marble, Slate and Stone Polishers, Etc., 1963-1972 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America, 1962-1965 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- National Maritime Union of America, 1962-1972 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Masters, Mates and Pilots, 1962-1972 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, 1966-1976 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Mechanics Educational Society of America, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  January and October 1972
- National Association of Special Delivery Messengers, 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  September 1966, 1968
- Metal Polishers, Buffers, Platers and Helpers International Union, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  October 19 1964
- Michigan State AFL-CIO, 1967-1969 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Milwaukee County Labor Council, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  October 29 1964 - September 10 1965
- International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  April and May 1962
- United Mine Workers of America, 1948-1969 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- T.S. Miners' International Federation, 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Minnesota AFL-CIO (Box 4, Folder 42)
  Postcard
- Mississippi AFL-CIO, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  May 11 1964
- International Union of Molders and Allied Workers, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  January 6 and 17 1972
- American Federation of Musicians, 1965-1978 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- National Advisory Committee on Farm Labor, 1962-1968 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- National Association of Government Employees, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- National Industrial Workers Union, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  December 2 1963
- Negro American Labor Council, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  November 11 1969
- Nevada State AFL-CIO, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  November 20 1963
- New Brunswick Federation of Labour (Box 4, Folder 51)
- New Jersey State AFL-CIO, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  June 5 1961 - October 25 1962
- New Mexico State AFL-CIO, 1963-1969 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  January 17 1963 - January 14 1969
- New York City Central Labor Council AFL-CIO, 1963-1970 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  November 6 1963 - April 17 1970
- New York State AFL-CIO, 1963-1977 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  November 26 1963 - April 20 1977
- New York State Union Label and Service Trades Department, AFL-CIO, 1953-1961 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  July 9 1953 - January 5 1961
- New York Veteran Police Association, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  February 12 1976
- Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union of New York and Vicinity, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 58)
- American Newspaper Guild, 1963-1972 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  April 24 1963 - January 5 1972
- Niagara County Council AFL-CIO, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  July 31 and August 4 1964
- NLRB Professional Association, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 61)
- NLRB Union, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  February 2 1972
- North Carolina AFL-CIO, 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  April 1 1964 - May 21 1968
- North Dakota AFL-CIO, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  January 17 1968
- Ohio AFL-CIO, 1962-1970 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  October 2 1962 - January 5 1970
- Office and Professional Employees, 1968-1972 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  July 29 1968 - January 20 1972
- Office Employees International Union, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  March 29 and September 14 1965
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, 1964-1977 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  March 16 1964 - October 14 1977
- Oklahoma State AFL-CIO, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  February 23 1962
- Ontario Federation of Labour, 1963-1971 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  November 29 1963 - July 12 1971
- Osterreichischer Gewerkschaftsbund, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  June 14 1978
- Oswego County Labor C=council, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 72)
- National Brotherhood of Packinghouse and Dairy Workers (AFL-CIO), 1963 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  June 4 1963
- United Packinghouse, Food and Allied Workers AFL-CIO, 1962-1968 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  March 26 1962 - September 19 1968
- International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  January 11 and March 16 1972
- United Papermakers and Paperworkers, 1966-1972 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  November 17 1966 - January 5 1972
- United Paperworkers International Union, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  December 4 1972 - November 13 1973
- Patrolmen's Benevolent Association, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  February 18 1969
- Pattern Makers League of North America, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  January 5 and 13 1972
- Independent Petroleum Workers Union, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  April 28 1970
- International Union of Petroleum and Industrial Workers, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  April 18 1977
- International Photoengravers Union of North America AFL-CIO, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  February 23 and 27 1956
- United Plant Guard Workers International Union, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  June 7 1978
- International Association of Operative Plasterers and Masons, 1962-1967 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  December 3 1962 - September 19 1967
- United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipefitting Industry of the US and Canada, 1963-1976 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  May 21 1963 - February 24 1976
- International Police Associations, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  April 25 and 30 1968
- Montreal Policemen's Brotherhood, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  July 17 1970
- Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  March 24 1964
- National Association of Postmasters of the U.S., 1972 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  February 22 and 29 1972
- Post Office Motor Vehicle Employees National Federation, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  September 1 1966
- United federation of Postal Clerks AFL-CIO, 1962-1969 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  February 5 1962 - February 18 1969
- National Association of Postal Supervisors, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 92)
- Postal Telegraph and Telephone International, 1963-1968 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  April 5 1963 - January 26 1968
- National Postal Union, 1969-1972 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  January 7 1969 - January 18 1972
- National League of the Postmasters of the U.S., 1965 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  April 1 1965
- International Brotherhood of Operative Potters, 1962-1967 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  February 19 1962 - October 16 1967
- International Brotherhood of Potter and Allied Workers, 1972-1977 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  January 12 1972 - April 18 1977